[
  {
    "QUESTION": "Tasty Pizza in Omaha, NE named a pizza after this 90s dance: \"________\" pizza",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Macarena",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Tootsee Roll"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Point Pleasant, WV celebrates a historic local monster with an annual \"________\" festival",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Mothman",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Wicked Witch"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Every May, Conway, AR drunkenly celebrates sucking on what creature?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Toad",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Snail"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What's the name of the private road leading up to Constipation Ridge in Fannie, AR?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Farfrompoopen Rd",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Hardstool Road"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION":  "Halifax, NS named three parrallel streets: This St, That St and \"________\". Dont get lost.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "The Other St",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "The St"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What road in Canyon County, Idaho is named after something tasty?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Chicken Dinner Road",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Candy Lane Rd"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Fountain, Colorado has a street sign: \"A Dog Will Lick His Butt But Won't Eat A ________\" Rd.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Pickle",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Lemon"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "An 18th century stable-boy misspelled 'Potatoes' when naming his racehorse: \"________\"",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Potoooooooo",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "patatos"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "At MonMouth Park, a horse raced named \"________\" hilariously raced against one named \"Thewifedoesntknow\"",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Mywifenosevrything",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Sleepingwithmysecretary"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "An infamous New Zealand racehorse was named \"________.\" (Pronounced 'Why kick a moo cow')",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Waikikamukau",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "wikykumoocoi"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "This Texas AA baseball team starts each game feeling like the ultimate underdogs. They are the Amarillo \"________\".",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Dirt Puppies",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Game Losers"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Fans of Jacksonville, Florida's AAA baseball team cover themselves in what sea creature?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Jumbo Shrimp",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Seahorse"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What seafood-inspired ice cream flavor does The Charmery in Maryland serve?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Old Bay",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Rocky Shores"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "\"Sweet Rock Ice Cream\" in Newfoundland has broken all ice cream rules by serving their bright red \"________\" flavor.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Devil's Footprints",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Stranger Things"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "North Carolina's \"________\" ice cream with ghost peppers requires customers sign a legal waiver",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Cold Sweat",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Ghostbuster"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Humans eating at this dangerously named food-truck in Tucson, AZ are taking their lives into their own hands.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Serial Grillers",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Poison Panini"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Pun-loving humans in Seattle might choose to eat at this food truck just for the spicey wordplay.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Naansense",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Cumin For Dinner"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What was the name of the Vietnamese food truck that went internet viral for their controversial sign?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Pho King",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Pho Inches Is Plenty"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Australian children might want to avoid this nightmare-inducing food truck: \"________\"",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Frying Nemo",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Snakes on a Plate"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Portland's Voodoo Doughnut sells this jelly-filled treat inspired by what late rapper?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Old Dirty Bastard",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Tupac"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Fitznuggy's in Massachusetts named their tuna sandwich after which iconic duo: \"________ Tuna\"",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Ike and Tina",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Shaq and Kobe"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What Northern California marijuana strain sounds like a smelly jungle disease?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Purple Monkey Balls",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Zika Fever"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Maine dispensaries sell what strain of marijuana that sounds like a bad wrestling move?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Slap N Tickle",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "The Ball Flicker"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "At Indiana's Candle Daddy store, what does \"M.I.L.F\" stand for?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Melts Into Lasting Fragrance",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Matches I'd Like to Flick"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Kurt Braunohler and Scotty Landes host what phallic-named comedy podcast?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Bananas",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Rocket in my Pocket"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "This award-winning audio podcast is all about the ghosts that haunt the small town of Biggleswade, England.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Weird in the Wade",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Spirits & Scones"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Band \"Naked Roommate\" released what 2024 song about showering together with your friends?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Pass the Loofah",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Bubble Bath Bros"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What $49.95 infomercial product uses military-grade technology to absorb your spouse's flatulence?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Better Marriage Blanket",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Fart Cartridge"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What late-night infomercial promised to helps golfers practice their game while on the toilet?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Potty Putter",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Hole In Two"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "This unnecessary, but real informercial product was for a stuffed animal to be worn under your car's seatbelt.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Tiddy Bear",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Safety Sam"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "This early 2000s infomercial promised instant 'bootylicious' results just by wearing these undies with padding built in.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Booty Pop",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Cushionel"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "A Los Angeles trivia team named themselves after what trivia rule violation?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "We Googled It",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Hidden Phones Club"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "An online review of the Hutzler Banana Slicer praised what lesser-known feature?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Saliva-free way of slicing bananas",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "You get to pick the thickness!"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Baby strollers often display this warning label for human parents that lack common sense.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Remove child before folding",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Do not pull behind car"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What candidate name caused a stink on a New Hampshire election ballot?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Dick Swett",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Gina Lipps"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What was the name of Talkeetna, Alaska's honorary cat-mayor for more than 20 years?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Whiskers",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Snowball"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "In Tongue, Scotland road signs feature what terrifying creature attacking cars?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Octopus",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Wildcat"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "In Dildo NL, you'll find a naughty little road named \"Captain ________ Crescent\".",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Willy Jackman",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Crotchet"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Humans in Yellowknife, NT are apt to regret taking a left turn down \"________ Road\".",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Ragged Ass",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Ohdamn"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Nederland, Colorado celebrate the death and cryogenic freezing of a beloved local figure with what festival?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Frozen Dead Guy Days",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Frosty Father Fest"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Yale, Michigan crowns local royalty at their annual lunch-themed \"________ Festival\" every July",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Bologna",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "juicebox"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Scented candle company \"Yankee Candle\" produces this scent for male humans with smelly homes.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Man Town",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Bachelor Pad Paradise"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "The innovators at \"Yankee Candle\" cannot be stopped. There breakfast themed scent is called \"________\".",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Mmm, Bacon!",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Waffle House"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Memphis, Tennessee has a politician claiming to be from planet Zambodia. His alien name is Prince \"________\"",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Mongo",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Zeeka"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "This podcast all about \"The Muppets\" might leave you feeling unsatisfied.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Getting Felt Up",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Hand to Mouth"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Humans named Luba, Becca and Erin can be heard sharing naughty secrets in their podcast: \"________\".",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Between Both Cheeks",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Under The Covers"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "This popular podcast about human health sounds pretty icky if you ask me.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "What's That Rash",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "So Many Fluids"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "This podcast tragically ran just 3 episodes in 2024 and was 'a podcast by dog groomers, for dog groomers'",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "The Dingleberry Fairies",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Between Two Furballs"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Host Jessica recommends burnt bean water when tuning into her anatomically confusing podcast: \"________\".",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "In Your Ear Balls",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Funny Bones To Pick"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Alliance, Nebraska has a bizarre American tribute to England's Stonehenge appropriately titled: \"________-henge\"",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Car",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Phone"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Mecca, California has this peculiar but nutritious museum: \"The International ________ Museum\".",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Banana",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Protein"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "North Dakota's Enchanted Highway features massive sculptures of \"________\", geese and fish.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Grasshoppers",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Wolves"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "In Rockport MA, there remains a house built in the 1920's made entirely of what?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Newspapers",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Popsicle Sticks"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "In Massachusetts, you might pass \"The Museum of ________\" and wonder if it's worth the price of admission.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Bad Art",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Butt-holes"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "How many feet long is the world's largest ball of twine, located in Cawker City, Kansas?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "8 Million",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "750,000"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Ashburn, Georgia has the world's biggest \"________\" with a creepy smile painted on the side.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Peanut",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Peach"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Travelers in Cottonwood, ID have two options: A normal hotel and a one-of-a-kind inn with this unusual shape.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Dog",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Apple"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Humans in Collinsville, IL painted the \"World's Biggest ________\" on a water tower.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Ketchup Bottle",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Cupcake"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Which year did Harold Davisson love so much that he created a 45-ton time capsule of it in Nebraska?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": 1975,
    "ROBOT ANSWER": 1969
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "In an unexpected twist you can find a Garden full of Buddhas in Arlee, Montana. How many are there?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": 1000,
    "ROBOT ANSWER": 222
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "How many chickens can be cooked simultaneously in the world's largest frying pan in Rose Hill, NC?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": 365,
    "ROBOT ANSWER": 99
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Once a year in South Dakota, burly men gather to wrestle in this delicious food.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Mashed Potatos",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Macaroni and Cheese"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Middleton, WI must have picked late at the museum draft. They got \"The National ________ Museum\".",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Mustard",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Belly Button"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "How many people live in Buford, Wyoming - America's smallest town?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": 1,
    "ROBOT ANSWER": 12
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "How old was Dorset, Minnesota's unusually young mayor elected in 2012?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": 3,
    "ROBOT ANSWER": 10
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What's been banned in Singapore public places since 1992?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Chewing gum",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Velcro shoes"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "American President John Quincky Adams kept what creature as a pet in the White House bathroom?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Alligator",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Piranha"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What did John Young smuggle onto the space shuttle Gemini 3 in 1965?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "corned beef sandwich",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "harmonica"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "How many seconds long is the world's longest recorded human burp?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": 73,
    "ROBOT ANSWER": 44
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "How many hot dogs can the human stomach theoretically hold?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": 74,
    "ROBOT ANSWER": 18
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What was bubble wrap originally invented to be used as?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "3D wallpaper",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Space pillows"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "New Year's Eve 2011, 5000 \"________\" fell from the sky in Beebe, Arkansas.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "dead blackbirds",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "fake butterflies"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What romance novel features a love interest that's literally just a weather event?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Taken by the Tornado",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Earthquakin'"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "How long is Portland, Oregon's Mill Ends Park, the world's smallest park?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "2 feet",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "21 feet"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What was the cancelled 1990 sitcom about Hitler living next to a Jewish couple?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Heil Honey I'm Home",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Be Mein"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Owner, Harry leads you to into his basement in New Carrollton, MD: Home of \"the Museum of ________\".",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Menstruation",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Toenails"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Hundreds of pounds of what delicious meal mysteriously appeared in the New Jersey woods?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Pasta",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Mashed Potatoes"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "A Japanese teacher lost their job in 2025 for having what side-hustle?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "convenience store clerk",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Stripper"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What did a Wisconsin pizzeria accidentally poison 80 people with in 2024?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "THC",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Magic Mushrooms"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "California wild pigs are mysteriously turning what bright color?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Neon Blue",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Magenta"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What did 15th century humans mistranslate and start eating to cure headaches?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Mummies",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Snake heads"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What did 1 million passengers sue two airlines for in a recent class action lawsuit?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Windowless window seats",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Bathroom surcharges"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "A 1980's news program's gave these wealth tips: Get a job, Borrow money, and \"________\".",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Marry a rich very sick person",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Sell your belongings"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What is a Denmark zoo feeding animals to save on costs?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Your dog",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Recycled paper"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Boston mayoral candidate \"________ ________\" struggled due to this unfortunate name similarity.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Geoffery Epstein",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Harvey Whinestine"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "How old is Govinda from Bankatwa, India who bit a cobra to death?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": 2,
    "ROBOT ANSWER": 11
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What old fashion trend have Zambian chimps resurrected?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Sticks in their butts",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Grass skirts"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What did a woman do on web camera that got her booted from Detroit court?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Making a sandwich",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Changing her clothes"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What brand mascot was arrested in Florida for credit card fraud?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Chuck E Cheese",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Trix Rabbit"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "A Mobile, AB coffee employee needed rabies shots after what pet jumped through the drive-thru window?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Monkey",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Raccoon"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What procedure did a Taiwan plastic surgeon perform on himself and post on social media?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Vasectomy",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Penis enlargement"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "In the name of equality, a Chinese influencer is calling guys to start wearing \"________\", on par with a bra.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "adams apple cover",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "ballbag"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Beeston, England residents are perplexed by random monthly appearances of what around town?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "peeled bananas",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "beans on toast"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "What did Minnesota Golden Gophers dump on their coach after beating Virginia Tech?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Mayonaise",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Lite beer"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "How many hours did the winner of China's 'don't touch your phone challenge' last?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": 1,
    "ROBOT ANSWER": 24
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Jimmy, Jonny and Denzale smoke marijuana and discuss fairy tales on what podcast?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Blunts Upon A Time",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Three Little Spliffs"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Host Sean asks what all-important question about art in his comedy podcast title?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Is Art Shit?",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "WTF?"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "For young audiences, the podcast \"Atomic ________\" sounds more gross than educational.",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "Booger",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Pizza"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Todd Parker and the Witches released what nerve-wracking song title?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "The Witch Is Dead",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Band of Bodies"
  },
  {
    "QUESTION": "Where did Psychedelic Porn Crumpets find God in their biggest hit song?",
    "CORRECT ANSWER": "In a tomato",
    "ROBOT ANSWER": "Up your nose"
  }
]